var triviaQuestions = [ {
    question: "Who does HUlk call 'puny god' while throwing them around like a rag doll?",
    options: [
        "Thor",
        "Loki",
        "Captian America",
        "Iron Man",
    ],
    answer: "Loki"
},
{
    question: "With what is Loki able to control minds?",
    options: [
        "Sceptre",
        "Mjolnir",
        "Stick",
        "Shield",
    ],
    answers: "Sceptre"
},
{
    question: "Where was Captain America at the start of the movie?",
    options: [
        "Hospital",
        "Aircraft",
        "Gym",
        "Home",
    ],
    answers: "Gym"
},
{
    question: "What does Captain America bring to the fight?",
    options: [
        "His shield",
        "Mjolnir",
        "Sword",
        "Bow & Arrow",
    ],
    answers: "His shield"
},
{
    question: "What is the name of Thor's hammer?", 
    options: [
        "Jupiter",
        "Hammer",
        "Smasher",
        "Mjolnir",
    ],
    answers: "Mjolnir"
},
{
    question: "Who was the first Avenger?",
    options: [
        "Thor",
        "Loki",
        "Captian America",
        "Iron Man",
    ],
    answer: "Captain America"
},
{
    question: "Who attacked New York?",
    options: [
        "Thanos",
        "Loki",
        "Asgardians",
        "Chitauri",
    ],
    answers: "Chitauri"
},
{
    question: "Who was mind controlled by Loki?",
    options: [
        "Steve Rogers",
        "Black Widow",
        "Hawkeye",
        "Nick Fury",
    ],
    answers: "Hawkeye"
},
{
    question: "What is Black Widows name?",
    options: [
        "Pepper Potts",
        "Natasha Romanoff",
        "Nebula",
        "Jane Foster",
    ],
    answers: "Natasha Romanoff"
},
{
    question: "Who is the executive director of S.H.I.E.L.D?", 
    options: [
        "Nick Fury",
        "Clint Barton",
        "Bruce Banner",
        "Erik Selvig",
    ],
    answers: "Nick Fury"
},
{
    question: "How many Avengers are there?", 
    options: [
        "9",
        "6",
        "4",
        "7",
    ],
    answers: "6"
},
{
    question: "What is Hawkeye's speciality?",
    options: [
        "Swords",
        "Nunchucks",
        "Boomerang",
        "Bow & Arrow",
    ],
    answer: "Bow & Arrow"
},
{
    question: "Where does Natasha find Bruce?",
    options: [
        "China",
        "London",
        "India",
        "Mexico",
    ],
    answers: "India"
},
{
    question: "What is Tony Starks superpower?",
    options: [
        "Iron Man",
        "Super strength",
        "Super speed",
        "Flying",
    ],
    answers: "Iron Man"
},
{
    question: "Whose death resulted in a turning point for the team?",
    options: [
        "Pepper Potts",
        "Phil Coulson",
        "Nebula",
        "Jane Foster",
    ],
    answers: "Phil Coulson"
}
];